<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<release id="7.0.0">
  <release>7.0.0</release>
  <date>03 Dec 2015</date>
  <version>
    <major>7</major>
    <minor>0</minor>
    <release>0</release>
  </version>
  <source>
    <source>
      <filename>php-7.0.0.tar.bz2</filename>
      <name>PHP 7.0.0 (tar.bz2)</name>
      <sha256>a92a54306832167a39f7c0ec00524fc6f3f7d985c806caa7632561d0ddedfcea</sha256>
      <md5/>
      <date>03 Dec 2015</date>
    </source>
    <source>
      <filename>php-7.0.0.tar.gz</filename>
      <name>PHP 7.0.0 (tar.gz)</name>
      <sha256>d6ae7b4a2e5c43a9945a97e83b6b3adfb7d0df0b91ef78b647a6dffefaa9c71b</sha256>
      <md5/>
      <date>03 Dec 2015</date>
    </source>
    <source>
      <filename>php-7.0.0.tar.xz</filename>
      <name>PHP 7.0.0 (tar.xz)</name>
      <sha256>7dbdda74c502960febe0544b3e3a7c430389a7a4260e94c73fd8ca26c33b8540</sha256>
      <md5/>
      <date>03 Dec 2015</date>
    </source>
  </source>
  <tags/>
  <announcements>
    <announcement lang="en">



     <p>The PHP development team announces the immediate availability of PHP
     7.0.0. This release marks the start of the new major PHP 7 series.
     </p>
     <p>
     PHP 7.0.0 comes with a new version of the Zend Engine, numerous improvements
     and new features such as
     </p>
     <ul>
        <li>Improved performance: PHP 7 is up to twice as fast as PHP 5.6</li>
	<li>Significantly reduced memory usage</li>
        <li>Abstract Syntax Tree</li>
        <li>Consistent 64-bit support</li>
        <li>Improved Exception hierarchy</li>
	<li>Many fatal errors converted to Exceptions</li>
	<li>Secure random number generator</li>
        <li>Removed old and unsupported SAPIs and extensions</li>
        <li>The null coalescing operator (??)</li>
        <li>Return and Scalar Type Declarations</li>
        <li>Anonymous Classes</li>
	<li>Zero cost asserts</li>
     </ul>


     <p>
     The <a href="http://php.net/manual/migration70.php">migration guide</a> is available in the PHP Manual. Please consult
     it for the detailed list of new features and backward incompatible changes.
     </p>

     <p>
     The inconvenience of the release lateness in several time zones is caused by the need to ensure the
     compatibility with the latest OpenSSL 1.0.2e release. Thanks for the patience!
     </p>

     <p>
     It is not just a next major PHP version being released today.
     The release being introduced is an outcome of the almost two years development
     journey. It is a very special accomplishment of the core team. And, it is a
     result of incredible efforts of many active community members.
     Indeed, it is not just a final release being brought out today, it is the rise of
     a new PHP generation with an enormous potential.
     </p>

     <p>Congratulations everyone to this spectacular day for the PHP world!</p>
     <p>Grateful thanks to all the contributors and supporters!</p>


</announcement>
  </announcements>
  <changes/>
</release>
