<?xml version="1.0"?>
<conference version="1">
  <id>php-tek-2019</id>
  <title>php[tek] 2019</title>
  <start_date>2019-05-21</start_date>
  <end_date>2019-05-21</end_date>
  <location country=""/>
  <summary type="text">We are announcing some exciting changes to [php\[tek\]](https://tek.phparch.com/?utm_campaign=phpnet2019) in 2019, our 14th consecutive year for this event!</summary>
  <content type="markdown">We are announcing some exciting changes to [php\[tek\]](https://tek.phparch.com/?utm_campaign=phpnet2019) in 2019, our 14th consecutive year for this event!

Once again we'll be taking place in [Atlanta](https://tek.phparch.com/venue/?utm_campaign=phpnet2019) in May, but this year we are moving to 3 full days of conference sessions: May 21-23

However, the significant change is in us creating a curated educational experience for our attendees, with all brand new talks being made just for this event.

You see this year we organized php\[tek\] into a [series of tracks](https://tek.phparch.com/tracks/?utm_campaign=phpnet2019), each dedicated to teaching you in-depth information about a specific topic. Leading these tracks are hand-selected [track chairs](https://tek.phparch.com/speakers/?utm_campaign=phpnet2019), chosen for their knowledge in the field and excellent presenters. They are all working together to create a unique curriculum to take your skills to the next level.

Each track&#x2019;s design is a [series of new talks](https://tek.phparch.com/schedule/?utm_campaign=phpnet2019) that flow together smoothly, and yet, you can drop in/out of a track throughout the day as needed. Each session is in a 1-hr timeslot. You can choose to sit in one room all day and learn a topic from beginning to end or bounce between the various tracks, putting together a unique learning experience tailored to your needs. The choice is yours.

We hope that you [choose to join us ](https://tek.phparch.com/registration/?utm_campaign=phpnet2019)for this unique experience. [Ticket sales are open](https://tek.phparch.com/registration/?utm_campaign=phpnet2019) with a few different price points, and the earlier you buy, the more you save.

See you in Atlanta!</content>
  <updated>2019-01-29T17:59:31+00:00</updated>
  <logo width="338" height="150">c011838a1b160e3e525caffc44124a48d8fb5dfc96fcf81f9df85719c445dbf1.jpg</logo>
</conference>
